Persico, Joseph; Papers apap030
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New York State Government Career, 1910-1981; 1; 9.8 cubic ft.
  - Subject Files, 1947-1976; 1.2
    - Attica, 1971-1972 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Basic Documents, Undated (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Blacks, 1975; Undated (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Buckley, 1968-1974 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - CIA Commission, 1975 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Campaign 1964, 1964-1976 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Campaign 1966 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Campaign 1968, 1967-1968 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Campaign 1970, 1970-1975 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - Campaign 1972 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Campaign 1976, 1973-1976 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Campaign Spending, 1966-1976 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - College, 1973 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Confirmation, 1974 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 21)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1967 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 22)
    - Coordinator of Inter American Affairs, 1947 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 23)
    - Costa Rica, 1972 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 24)
    - Critical Choices, 1972-1976 (Box 18 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 25)
    - Daily Schedules, 1975-1977 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - De Toqueville, 1974 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Death Penalty, 1973 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Defense, Undated (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1966-1970 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Draft, Undated (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Drugs, 1970-1975 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Dyslexia, 1975-1976 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Education, 1967-1969 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Empire State Plaza, 1970-1978 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Energy Independence Authority, 1975-1979 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Falconry, 1973 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Farmers, Undated (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Federal Aid, 1964-1976 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Filibuster, 1975; Undated (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Fine, William F., 1980 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - 'Firsts' in New York State, Undated (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Food, 1974 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1973-1979 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - Garbage Strike, 1968 (Box 19 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1964-1974 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Governor's Club, Undated (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Health, 1964-1966 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
      (including Pollution issues).
    - Historic Preservation, 1972-1977 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - History, 1972-1976 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Humor, 1964-1976; Undated (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Intern Interview, 1975 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Italian Americans, 1955-1973 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Kendall, Kathleen E., 1974 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1968-1980 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Latin America, 1961-1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Argentina, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Barbados, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Bolivia, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Brazil, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Columbia, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Costa Rica, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Dominican Republic, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Ecuador, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, El Salvador, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Guatemala, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 21)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Guyana, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 22)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Haiti, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 23)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Honduras, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 24)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Jamaica, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 25)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Mexico, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 26)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Nicaragua, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 27)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Panama, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 28)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Paraguay, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 29)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Peru, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 30)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Trinidad-Tobago, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 31)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Uruguay, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 32)
    - Latin American Mission Speeches, Venezuela, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 33)
    - Latin American Mission, Receipts, 1969 (Box 20 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 34)
    - Lefkowitz, L., 1979 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Lincoln, A., Undated (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Long Island Bridge, 1973 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Lottery, 1967 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - Lubell, S., 1970 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Writing, 1968-1981 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Montesacro, 1972 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Monthly Calendars, 1968-1977 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Nakasian, S., 1968 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - National Caucus of Labor Committees, 1974 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Nursing Homes, 1973-1975 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Philanthropies, 1965-1966 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Pocantico, 1972-1976 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Polls, 1968-1974 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Presidency, 1968-1973 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Press, 1970-1975 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - Program Papers, ca. 1960s-1970s) (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Mrs. [Happy] Rockefeller, 1969-1976 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Death, 1979 (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1958-1979; Undated (Box 21 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Rockefeller Family, 1910-1979; Undated (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Photos, 1970s-1981 (mostly Undated) (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Salaries & Bookkeeping Materials, 1968-1975 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Slote, Les, 1981 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - Source Speeches, 1963-1976 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Speechwriting, 1968-1976; Undated (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Staff, 1969-1974 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Swearing In, 1974 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Transportation, 1970-1973 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Tri-Lateral Commission, 1981 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Urban Development Corporation, 1968-1975 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Vice Presidency, 1955-1977 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Viet Nam, 1968-1975 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Watergate, 1973-1974 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Women, Undated (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - White House Staff, 1976 (Box 22 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - Admiral's House Pamphlet, 1975 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Campaign Material Pamphlets, 1960s-1970s; Undated (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Critical Choices for Americans Pamphlets, 1970s (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Ford, Gerald, Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - Historic Preservation Pamphlets, 1976 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Pocantico Pamphlets, late 1970s; Undated (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Collection Catalog, Undated (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Death Pamphlets, 1979-1980 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Nelson Rockefeller: A Biography by Joe Alex Morris. New York: Harper & Brothers, 1960 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Nomination of Nelson A. Rockefeller of New York to be Vice President of the United States. Hearings Before the Committee on Rules and Administration. United States Senate, 1974 (Box 23 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
  - Newsclippings, 1968-1975; 1.3
    - Abortion, 1972 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Adirondack State Park, 1969-1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Arts, 1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1967-1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - Campaigns, 1966-1974 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - Cities, 1969-1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, 1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1967-1968 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Consumers, 1970-1972 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Courts, 1969-1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Crime, 1967-1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Death Penalty, 1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Drugs, 1966-1974 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Education, 1969-1971 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - Energy, 1975 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Environment, 1969-1971 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - Ford, 1979 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Foreign Affairs, 1967-1971 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Governors/ Wilson, 1973-1974 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - Health, 1968-1971 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Israel, Rockefeller Statements, 1968-1971 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 21)
    - Italian Americans, ca. 1970s (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 22)
    - Javits, Jacob K, 1967 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 23)
    - Jobs, 1967-1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 24)
    - Kennedy, Robert F, 1968-1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 25)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1968-1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 26)
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1973 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 27)
    - Latin America (English and Spanish), 1969 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 28)
    - Levitt, Arthur, 1972 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 29)
    - Lindsay, John, 1967-1970 (Box 24 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 30)
    - Mass Transportation, 1968-1974 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 1)
    - Medicaid, 1967-1968 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 2)
    - Morrow, Hugh, 1969 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 3)
    - Motor Vehicles, 1970-1973 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 4)
    - News Media, 1968-1973; Undated (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 5)
    - New York City, 1967-1969 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 6)
    - Persico, Joseph E., 1969-1978 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 7)
    - Police, 1972 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 8)
    - Public Employees, 1960s-1973 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 9)
    - Republican Party, 1969-1975 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 10)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1969-1972 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 11)
    - Riots, 1968 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 12)
    - Rockefeller Family, Undated (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1971-1975 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 14)
    - State Fair, 1969 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 15)
    - Speeches, 1968-1979 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 16)
    - SUNY, 1968-1970 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 17)
    - Vietnam, 1968 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 18)
    - Voting, 1969 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 19)
    - Watergate, 1973 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 20)
    - Welfare, 1967-1968 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 21)
    - White House Mess, 1980; Undated (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 22)
    - Women, 1967-1973 (Box 25 (1-New York State Government Career), Folder 23)
    - Rockefeller, Photographs, 1974 (Oversized 26, Folder 1)
- Writings, ca. 1930s-2001; 2; 18.23 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  This series relates to his writings, both published and unpublished, which include book reviews, essays, magazine articles, newspaper articles and op-eds, non-fiction books, novels, plays, and television scripts. It contains correspondence, including e-mails (Persico's correspondence is not limited to folders labeled as such); contracts; drafts; event materials, interview questions and transcripts; memoranda; notes (he often wrote them on index cards); photographs; press clippings; research materials; scrapbooks; and speeches related to Persico's various writings. Notable research materials include copies of American intelligence and military communications and reports and copies of the correspondence of famous individuals, such as Franklin Delano Roosevelt. Some items, such as correspondence and research materials, are in French or German. Some correspondence relating to Persico's writings can be found in Series 3: Biographical. The materials often reference individuals with whom Persico collaborated. His daughter Vanya Maria Persico (he often referred to by her initials in his papers) assisted her father with clerical duties, such as typing up drafts of manuscripts, during the process of researching and writing his books. Robert (Bob) Loomis was Joe Persico's editor at Random House.
  - Piercing the Reich, 1940-1979; 2.1; 1.4 cubic ft.
    The Piercing the Reich subseries is primarily Persico's research material. The majority of the material is copies of declassified FBI files and the OSS War Report. The Writings subseries includes scripts for the History Channel documentaries "Piercing the Reich: The Deadly Deceivers" and "Nuremberg: Tyranny on Trial" in the "Documentaries, Narration" folder. Additional material collected and created by Persico during the writing of Piercing the Reich was deposited by Persico at the Hoover Institution Library and Archives at Stanford University. The finding aid for this material is available online through the Online Archive of California.
    - Piercing the Reich, 1970s. FBI Declassified Files, 1940s-1970s; 2.1.1
      - Angleton, James (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 1)
      - Bancroft, Mary (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 2)
      - Bank, Aaron (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 3)
      - Boyd, Ann (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 4)
      - British Intelligence (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 5)
      - Brittenham, Ray (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 6)
      - Bruce, David (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 7)
      - Burke, Mike (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 8)
      - Casey, William J. (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 9)
      - Cannoot, Ferdinand (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 10)
      - Chauefeur (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 11)
      - CIA Correspondence (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 12)
      - Chisel (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 13)
      - Copeland, Miles (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Miscellaneous (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 15)
      - Crocus (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 16)
      - Dartmouth (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 17)
      - Dawes, Houseboat (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 18)
      - Deadwood (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 19)
      - Dillon (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 20)
      - de Beaufort, Nam (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 21)
      - Doctor (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 22)
      - Downend (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 23)
      - Dupont (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 24)
      - European Interviews Correspondence (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 25)
      - Fleisher, Henry (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 26)
      - Gestapo (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 27)
      - Goldberg, Arthur (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 28)
      - Gould, Joseph (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 29)
      - Green - UP (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 30)
      - Grell, William (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 31)
      - Grimm, Kurt (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 32)
      - Hammer (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 33)
      - Helms, Richard (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 34)
      - Hoguet, Peter (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 35)
      - Hood, Cornelia (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 36)
      - Houston, Lawrence (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 37)
      - Hyde, Henry (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 38)
      - Haass, Walter (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 39)
      - Issikides, Barbara (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 40)
      - Italian Based Missions (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 41)
      - Joan, Eleanor (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 42)
      - Jolis, Albert (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 43)
      - Junk, Robert (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 44)
      - Karlow, Peter (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 45)
      - Katz, Milton (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 46)
      - Kirstein, Willi (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 47)
      - Kolbe, Fritz (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 48)
      - Laverge, Jan (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 49)
      - Lowenstein (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 50)
      - McCulloch (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 51)
      - Meucke, Carl (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 52)
      - Miller, Gerald (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 53)
      - Molden, Fritz (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 54)
      - Morgan, Henry (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 55)
      - Oakes, John (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 56)
      - OSS, History of (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 57)
      - OSS Organization Charts (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 58)
      - OSS Phone Book (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 59)
      - Painter (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 60)
      - Peenemunde (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 61)
      - Perry, Hart (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 62)
      - Photos (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 63)
      - Pratt, George (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 64)
      - Prester, Julio (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 65)
      - Questions of Interviewees (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 66)
      - Reddick, W.C. (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 67)
      - Roman, Howard (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 68)
      - Roosevelt, Kermit (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 69)
      - Rubens, Pauley (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 70)
      - Sichel, Peter (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 71)
      - Simpson (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 72)
      - Steiner, Herbert (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 73)
      - Strahles, Carl (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 74)
      - Sutton, Henry (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 75)
      - Swiss, O.P.S. (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 76)
      - Swiss Operations (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 77)
      - Teper, Lazare (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 78)
      - Thalberg, Hans (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 79)
      - Thompson, Robert E.S. (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 80)
      - Tofte, Hans (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 81)
      - Training Agents (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 82)
      - Turano, Anthony (Box 27 (2.1.1-Piercing the Reich), Folder 83)